(Bernadette:)'cause I was always
the smallest kid in school,
(Bernadette:)so I thought if I
became a scientist,
(Bernadette:)I could invent a formula
that made me taller.
(Amy:)That's cute.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, I thought it was working
for a while,
(Bernadette:)but then I found out
my brother was just
(Bernadette:)lowering the pencil marks
on the door frame.
(Bernadette:)How about you?
(Amy:)Oh, I guess it must have been
back when I was in the Girl Sprouts.
(Bernadette:)Girl Sprouts?
(Amy:)My mom made it up as an
alternative to the Girl Scouts.
(Amy:)She didn't want me selling cookies
on some street corner "like a whore."
(Bernadette:)How did that get
you into science?
(Amy:)Oh, I went to the library
and took out a book on biology
(Amy:)to see what whores did.
(Leonard:)On the one hand,
if I say yes...
(Penny:)This isn't funny anymore.
(Penny:)Just say no
so we're done with this.
(Penny:)Will you marry me or not?
(Leonard:)Ooh, interesting. Did you just
propose to me again?